

DANIELE QUINTILIANI

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT



+34 643 755 352



quintiliani.d@gmail.com



http://github.com/malethik



https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniele-quintiliani/

EDUCATION

ISDI CODERS ACCADEMY MADRID

Bootcamp Full Stack Web Developer 2023-2024

IPSIA EMILIO CAVAZZA, POMEZIA (ROMA)

FP2 chemistry and biology 2003-2006

COMPETENCIAS

- DOMINE OF: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, ANGULAR, NEST. TYPESCRIPT, EXPRESS, MYSQL, JEST, JASMINE, E2E
- FAMILIAR WITH: REACT, PYTHON, PHP, MONGODB, C#.
- Excelentes habilidades de resolución y depuracion.
- Altamente organizado y orientado al detalle.

LANGUAGES

- Italian (native)
- Español (bilingual)
- English (B2)

RESUMEN

Web developer with front and back end training.

My skills include: my ability to create clear and secure code, skills for integrating web technologies and designing attractive interfaces.

Expert in developing, testing and deploying web applications that meet customer needs and industry standards.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Project MotoMarket

Fullstack developer

2023 - Now

I developed an application entirely using the NestJS back framework, implementing the database with PostgreSQL and Prisma as ORM.

Implementation of an easy-to-use front design with HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript and using the latest version of Angular. Testing of unit, integration and E2E tests.

Using modern development tools like git and gitHub to collaborate on code and create version control.

RAAM Delivery Madrid

Administration 2020 - 2023

Use of computer and technological systems (Excel, Word). Coordination of work schedules and tasks of the team of 42 people.

Preparation of reports and periodic reports on the work schedule.

LA FUNDAMENTAL, Madrid

Waiter

2019 - 2020

NAF SERVIZI, Roma

Developer / Administration consulting 2012-2018

In charge of creating functional and intuitive pages and websites for clients using Wordpress.

Maintenance and updating of existing web applications to guarantee security and performance.

Use of computer and technological systems (Excel, Word). Third party management service.

HOBBIES

- Videogame arcade and vintage
- technology
- Moto custom
- Sci-fi
- TV Series
- Books
- Astronomy

EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

Ecosistem srl

edar technician 2010 - 2012

Responsible for coordinating and executing preventive maintenance operations on equipment, as well as guaranteeing the correct operation of this type of facilities.

Carry out analysis in each of the purification phases to verify its correct functioning.

Taking representative samples of influents and effluents.

Operation of separation, treatment and removal of sludge and waste.

Nacional Fire Department

Fireman 2008- 2010

Italians Army

Army 2006- 2008



